[{"id": 443, "question": "You could feel sorry for Alberto Torres, who is blind. The last thing he remembers seeing was his daughter being born 13 years ago. Then the world went blank; he can only imagine what his only child looks like now, as a teenaged honor student. Bad luck is no stranger to this warm and thoughtful 37-year-old man. His mother died of cancer when he was 4, and his father, who was often ill, had to give him up to the care of the state when he was 11. He later worked for 19 years in a workshop making household goods, deathly boring work. Earlier this month, Alberto Torres's wife, who had just been laid off from her job, had to have a breast removed due to cancer and now faces a year of radiation treatments. Things seemed always to go from almost incredibly bad to worse. Even Mr. Torres's good luc...\n\nQ: In the eyes of the writer, Alberto Torres is a man of   _  .", "options": ["deep thinking", "weak motivation", "special talents", "great independence"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2314, "question": "Unemployment in Europe has recently hit record highs. Although Denmark has been protected from economic problems thanks to its low public debt, qualified professionals are still finding it tough to get a job. Danish marketing firm Reputation Copenhagen has come up with a way of helping academics get noticed -- putting them on display in storefront windows. Many highly-trained professionals, ranging from former CEOs to lawyers and tax experts, are currently finding it increasingly difficult to find proper employment on the Danish job market. Some of them have been trying for years, leaving their resumes with dozens of companies, without ever hearing back from them, and are now at a point where they are willing to try anything, even putting themselves in display windows like goods, hoping to...\n\nQ: Some job-seekers are willing to put themselves in the windows to display in that   _  .", "options": ["they think it is fashionable", "their parents ask them to", "it's increasingly difficult to get hired", "they find it's interesting"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 663, "question": "The woman had died when the rescuers found her after the terrible earthquake. She was covered by a destroyed house. Through gaps of those ruins,the rescuers could see her last posture . It was something like an ancient person who was kowtowing ,but it just looked strange because she was out of shape by pressure. The rescuers confirmed her death by touching her through the gaps of the ruins. They shouted at the ruins again and again,knocked the bricks using various tools,but no reply inside. Then the rescuing team went to the next building. Suddenly the leader ran back,calling \"Come here.\" He came to the body,put his hands under the woman,feeling and touching,then shouted loudly and gladly,\"There is someone,a baby,still living.\" Through some efforts,rescuers cleaned up the ruins which block...\n\nQ: When the baby was rescued, he    .", "options": ["was smiling a lot", "was fast asleep", "was listening carefully", "was frightened to death"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1071, "question": "Best places to visit in Australia Are you looking for the best places to see in Australia? Here are the top 5 places to visit in Australia. It includes the best, the most beautiful and the most famous. Sydney For those who have made a flight from the other side of the world, if you come and don't see Sydney, it is a bit like going to Germany and not drinking a beer, or to England and not seeing London, or America and not trying a hot dog. There is plenty to see and do in Sydney apart from the well known attractions of the Harbour Bridge, the Opera House, and Bondi beaches. Byron Bay Located in New South Wales, just south of the Queensland border, Byron Bay is popular with not just international tourists, but is also a favorite holiday destination of Australians. The lighthouse is amazing a...\n\nQ: Which places will you go in Australia if you are interested in music?", "options": ["Sydney and the Great Barrier Reef", "Byron Bay and Daintree Rainforest", "The Great Ocean Roadand Byron Bay", "Byron Bay and Sydney"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2311, "question": "For years, I thought that my mother would become a Centenarian , but after 98 years and eight months, she recently died of old age. As it was with my father, her funeral took place in the most peaceful setting of the countryside of rural Washington County. Even after my father died, we continued to think of our parents as one. They were a team in the traditional sense. Church and family were their life- lines. They worked hard, never complaining. They expected to earn their daily bread by the sweat of their brow. Once during a conversation with Tom Brokaw, who wrote the best- selling hook The Greatest Generation, I told him, \"You left out my parents.\" They didn't go off to war, but they belonged to the Greatest Generation. They, too, were part of the foundation that made America truly grea...\n\nQ: What do we know about Tom Brokaw?", "options": ["He is one of the author's parents' friends.", "He likes talking with the author's parents.", "He takes up a position as a writer.", "He is good at managing a home."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1521, "question": "Dear Ana, In your last letter, you told me that your boss Stephanie was probably looking for a new job and you didn't know how to tell her that you wanted to take her position if she left. Well, I'd like to tell you that there is no polite way to talk about this situation with your boss. After all, you are not one-hundred-percent sure that she is actually job-hunting. Even if you know for sure that she is, you can't, because it's not your business. Still, there are a couple of things that you can do to put yourself in a good position in case your boss does _ in the near future. First, you can have a general conversation with her about your career plans. Say something like, \"You've always been supportive of me, Stephanie, and I'd love you to give me some advice on my professional developmen...\n\nQ: Which of the following didn't Liz ask Ana to do?", "options": ["To let her manager know her desire for training.", "To ask her boss if she needs any help from her.", "To ask her boss for advice on her career plans.", "To find out who is also trying to get that position."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1475, "question": "If you're a man and you're reading this, congratulations: you're a survivor. According to statistics, you're more than twice as likely to die of skin cancer than a woman, and nine times more likely to die of AIDS. Even if you make it to the end of your natural term, about 78 years for men in Australia, you'll die on average five years before a woman. There're many reasons for this--typically, men take more risks than women and are more likely to drink and smoke--but perhaps more importantly, men don't go to the doctor. \"Men aren't seeing doctors as often as they should,\" says Dr. Gullotta. \"This is particularly so for the over-40s, when chances of diseases are higher .\" Gullotta says a healthy man should visit the doctor every year or two. For those over 45, it should be at least once a ye...\n\nQ: What does Dr. Ross Cartmill mean by \"the ostrich approach\"? (Line 1, Para. 9)", "options": ["A serious attitude to one's health conditions.", "A new way to cure certain diseases.", "Refusal to get medical treatment for fear of the pain.", "Unwillingness to find out about one's disease because of fear."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3490, "question": "Have you ever suddenly felt that someone you knew was in trouble--and was he? Have you ever dreamed something that came true later? Maybe you have ESP . ESP stands for Extra Sensory Perception. It may be called a sixth sense. It seems to let people know about events before they happen, or events that are happening some distance away. Here's an example. A woman was ironing clothes. Suddenly she screamed, \"My father is dead! I saw him sitting in the chair!\" Just then, a telegram came. The woman's father died of a heart attack. He died sitting in a chair. There are thousands of stories like this one on record. Scientists are studying them to find out what's behind these strange mental messages. Here's another example--one of hundreds of dreams that have come true: A man dreamed he was walking...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the author believes that the sixth sense is  _  .", "options": ["in existence", "imaginative", "not real", "impossible"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2211, "question": "Christmas Day, the birthday of Jesus Christ, is the most important festival in prefix = st1 /Britainand some other countries. On Christmas Eve, people usually tell their children to put their stockings at the end of their beds before they go to sleep. Children believe Santa Claus, with the other name of Father Christmas, will come during the night and fill their stockings with Christmas presents. Actually , Father Christmas is children's father. He dresses up in a red coat and waits until children fall asleep. Then he goes into children's bedrooms, and puts small presents in their stockings. When children are no longer young, they know who Father Christmas really is. Not only children but also their parents enjoy Christmas stockings. They also have stockings. Early on the morning of Christ...\n\nQ: From the story we know that on Christmas Day children feel very happy because they can receive  _  .", "options": ["red clothes", "stockings", "presents", "food"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2940, "question": "Although most weddings follow long-held traditions, there's still room for American individualism. For example, the usual place for a wedding is in a church. But some people get married outdoors in a scenic spot. A few even have the ceremony while skydiving or riding on horseback! The couple may invite hundreds of people or just a few close friends. They choose their own style of colors, decorations and music during the ceremony. But some things rarely change. The bride usually wears a beautiful long white wedding dress. She traditionally wears \"something old, something new, something borrowed and something blue.\" The groom wears a formal suit. Several close friends participate in the ceremony as attendants, including the best man and the maid of honor. As the ceremony begins, the groom an...\n\nQ: Which of the following best shows American individualism?", "options": ["Most weddings observe long-held traditions.", "Some people choose their own style of weddings.", "People choose a church as a place for a wedding.", "The bride wears a beautiful long white wedding dress."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1880, "question": "Melissa Poe was 9 years old when she began a campaign for a cleaner environment by writing a letter to the then President Bush. Through her on efforts, her letter was reproduced on over 250 donated billboards across the country. The response to her request for help was so huge that Poe established Kids For A Cleaner Environment (Kids F.A.C.E.) in 1989. There are now 300,000 members of Kids F.A.C.E. worldwide and it is the world's largest youth environmental organization. Poe has also asked the National Park Service to carry out a \"Children's Forest\" project in every national park. In 1992, she was invited one of only six children in the world to speak at the Earth Summit in prefix = st1 /Brazilas part of the Voices of the future Program. In 1993, she was given a Caring Award for her effort...\n\nQ: Kid's Yards is   _  .", "options": ["established in national park", "started to protect wildlife", "a wildlife-raising project", "an environment park for kids"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 797, "question": "When I opened my e-mail the other day, a pretty woman named Rachel appeared on my computer screen. She greeted me by name and started talking with great enthusiasm . Every now and then she stopped to smile at me or blow a kiss. She was reading to me an e-mail from my brother, and a lot of it was about the trouble he had getting the phone company to give him a high-speed Internet connection. It was pretty cool. Rachel was there thanks to a new technology called Facemail. An ace man lets you send an e-mail that gets ready to the recipient by an attractive male or female from or by a clown . The software, which is free, can be downloaded at www.facemail.com. Facemail faces are lifelike, and they simulate emotions based on emotions-for example, that you put in your text. Type in; -x, and Rache...\n\nQ: The writer mentioned Nike website and Micheal Jordan to show that_.", "options": ["Facemail can make shopping on the Internet more interesting", "Nike company is increasing its sales through the fame of prefix = st1 /Jordan", "Michael Jordan will serve you himself on Nike website", "famous people like Micheal Jordan also like to use Facemail"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3168, "question": "\"Our aim is to take our art to the world and make people understand what it is to move,\" said David Belle, the cofounder of parkour . Do you love running? It is a good exercise, yet many people find it boring. But what if making your morning jog a creative one?Like jumping from walls and over gaps and ground rolls? Just like the James Bond in the movie Casino Royale? Bond jumps down from a roof to a windowsill and then runs several blocks over _ on the way. It is just because of Bond's wonderful performances that the sport has become popular worldwide. Yes, that's parkour, an extreme street sport aimed at moving from one point to another as quickly as possible, getting over all the obstacles in the path using only the abilities of the human body. Parkour is considered an extreme sport. As ...\n\nQ: Parkour has become popular throughout the world because of   _  .", "options": ["its cofounder, David Belle", "the film, Casino Royale", "its risks and tricks", "the varieties of participants"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2429, "question": "Big Brothers Big Sisters is based on the simplicity and power of friendship. It is a program which provides friendship and fun by matching _ (ages 7-17) with a volunteer adult who can be both a role model and a supportive friend. Volunteer tutors come from all walks of life--married, single, with or without children. Big Brothers and Big Sisters are not replacement parents or social workers. They are tutors: someone to trust, to have fun with, to talk and go to when needed. A Big Sister and Little Sister will generally spend between one and four hours together three or four times each month for at least twelve months. They enjoy simple activities such as a picnic at a park, cooking, playing sport or going to a football match. These activities improve the friendship and help the young perso...\n\nQ: What  is  the  aim  of  Big  Brothers  Big  Sisters?", "options": ["To offer students public services.", "To provide partnership and fun for young people.", "To organize sport activities for young people.", "To help students improve their grades."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 117, "question": "Winter is the time of year when people feel very blessed. This isn't because people feel thankful for the cold weather, nor because the important festivals---Christmas or Spring Festival---offer an excuse to celebrate. In fact, \"Bless you!\" is a common response if someone sneezes, a symptom of catching a cold or the flu. Colds and the flu are the most common illnesses of autumn and winter as the weather gets colder. Viruses cause them. If you get one you will feel annoyed, but it is not usually serious. The flu is spread from person to person when we come into contact with a person with the virus. We get the virus on our hands and then we touch our noses and our mouths. We can pass on the flu before we realize we have it. You can infect others one day before symptoms develop and for up to ...\n\nQ: We say \"Bless you!\" when   _  .", "options": ["we feel annoyed at someone.", "someone sneezes.", "someone catches a cold or the flu.", "we celebrate some important festivals."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1770, "question": "Who doesn't love sitting beside a cosy fire on a cold winter's night ? Who doesn't love to watch flames curling up a chimney? Fire is one of man's greatest friends, but also one of his greatest enemies. Many big fires are caused by carelessness. A lighted cigarette thrown out of a car or train window or a broken bottle lying on dry grass can start a fire. Sometimes, though, a fire can start on its own. Wet hay can begin burning by itself. This is how it happens: the hay starts to rot and begins to give off heat which is trapped inside it. Finally, it bursts into flames. That's why farmers cut and store their hay when it's dry. Fires have destroyed whole cities. In the 17th century, a small fire which began in a baker's shop burnt down nearly every building in London. Moscow was set on fire...\n\nQ: Which of the following describes the way how hay begins burning on its own ?", "options": ["wet hay ---- becomes dry ---- gives off heat ---- burns", "dry hay ---- gets too much heat from the sun ---- gives out heat --- starts to burn", "wet hay ---- begins to rot ---- gives out heat ---- starts to burn", "dry hay ---- gives off heat ---- starts to rot ---- starts to burn"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 596, "question": "Poet William Stafford once said that we are defined more by the detours in life than by the narrow road toward goals.I like this image.But it was quite by accident that I discovered the deep meaning of his words. For years we made the long drive from our home in Seattle to my parents' home in Boise in nine hours.We traveled the way most people do:the fastest,shortest,easiest road,especially when I was alone with four noisy,restless kids who hate confinement and have strong opinions about everything. Road trips felt risky,so I would drive fast,stopping only when I had to.We would stick to the freeways and arrive tired. But then Banner,our lamb was born.He was rejected by his mama days before our planned trip to Boise.I had two choices:leave Banner with my husband,or take him with me.My husb...\n\nQ: Why did the author use to take freeways to her parents'home?", "options": ["It was less tiring.", "It would be faster and safer.", "Her kids would feel less confined.", "She felt better with other drivers nearby."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 392, "question": "There's a man in the habit of hitting me on the head with an umbrella.At first I couldn't stand it;now I'm used to it. I don't know his name.I know he's average in appearance,wears a gray suit.and has a common face one hot morning,when 1 was sitting off a tree-shaded bench in Palermo Park,reading the paper,suddenly I felt something touch my head.It was the very same man who now,as I'm writing.keeps striking me with an umbrella. On that occasion I turned around filled with anger.He just kept on hitting me.I asked him if he was crazy.He didn't even seem to hear me.Thell I threatened to call a policeman.Calmly.cool as a cucumber,he stuck with his task.After a few moments of hesitation,and seeing that he was not about to change his attitude,I stood up and hit him on the nose.The man fell down....\n\nQ: When the man began to strike the author with an umbrella,the author", "options": ["became angry", "called the police", "turned around and escaped", "turned around and fought back"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1991, "question": "Recently, South Korean star PSY's 'Gangnam style\" video has been popular on the Internet. It has become most people's favorite music. In fact, the song has set the Guinness World Record for the most popular video in the history of the Internet. More than two million people have said \"like\" since the song was on the Internet on July 15. PSY\"s special dance moves and funny horse riding style have attracted many people. Although many people do not understand the language, the video has become the talk of the Internet. The song has come to first place in the music charts in 31 countries, including the United States, the United Kingdom, and Canada. \"I just sang for my South Korean fans. I have never expected it to be popular in other countries,\" PSY told the reporters on a concert. The song was...\n\nQ: What is the best title of the passage?", "options": ["Life of the Music Star PSY", "\"Gangnam Styly\" ---- Most people's favorite Music", "PSY's Famous Compositions", "Meaning of \"Gangnam Style\""], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1662, "question": "About 10 years ago, I started a job as a trainer for a telemarketing agency.In one of my first classes, the head trainer told a very inspiring story. He began by drawing a stickman standing in the middle of a circle.To make it more interesting, he drew things like a house, a car, and a few friends inside the circle. He asked the question, \"Can anyone tell me what this is?\" In a long silence, one guy decided to throw out \"the world?\" The trainer said, \"That's close and this is your Comfort Zone.Inside your circle you have all the things that are important to you.\" \"Your home, your family, your friends, and your job.People feel that inside this circle they are safe from any danger or conflict.\" \"Can anyone tell me what happens when you step out of this circle?\" A strong silence came over the...\n\nQ: Why does the author tell us the story?", "options": ["To build up our interpersonal skills.", "To make us work better as a team.", "To provide us some working activities.", "To motivate us to step out for a better world."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2393, "question": "Every child has written their names on the beach at some point. But whereas most people's \"handwriting\" is washed away, one super-rich Arab sheikh has ensure that his graffiti will last a little longer. Hamad Bin Hamdan Al Nahyan, 63, has scrawled his name in sand on an island he owns with letters so big that they be seen from space. The word \"HAMAD\" measures 1,000 meters high and is a staggering two miles long from the \"H\" to the \"D\" on the Al Futaisi Island. And rather than allow the writing to be washed away by the ocean, the letters actually form waterways that absorb the encroaching tide. The ruler's name is even visible on Google's map service. Hamad dreamed up the idea and had his workmen work hard for weeks to craft the enormous piece of sand graffiti. It is not known how much it c...\n\nQ: Which of the following might be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["The Rainbow Sheikh's name can be seen from space", "The richest Arab sheikh's name has made many funny things", "A great person likes doing things on a large scale", "A well-known philanthropist displays his wealth"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1640, "question": "Have you ever tried broccoli ice cream? That's what Oliver serves his customers in the new movie Oliver's Organic Ice Cream. The one-minute film was created by kids. A film is a movie. The young students learned their moviemaking skills at the Jacob Burns Film Center. The center is in Pleasantville, New York. Kids who go there learn how to make movies and music videos. The character Oliver and his treats are animated. In an animated movie, objects, such as ice cream and paper dolls, appear to be alive or moving. Animated movies are made up of hundreds of pictures. It takes 15 pictures to make just one second of film. To make a movie that lasts one minute, students need to take about 900 frames. A frame is a picture. Animation expert Joe Summerhays teaches kids the steps to shoot a movie. H...\n\nQ: What is the most important thing students learn by making a movie?", "options": ["The steps to shoot a movie.", "The skills in drawing pictures.", "The way of working with others.", "The importance of animation."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1820, "question": "Earth Day events are arranged all over the world, but for New Yorkers in the Catskill region, there are plenty of options.s6t---- Earth Day Celebrations6t---- Place: Frost Valley; Time: Friday, April 8 - Saturday, April 9 (Check-in at 5:00 pm on Friday). Activities include recycled arts and crafts projects, classes on composting and recycling, nature hikes, and a greenhouse planting project. All ages are welcomed. $15.00 per person (includes lunch). Kids 5 and under free. Call (845) 985-2291 for more details and to register.s6t---- Earth Festivals6t---- Place: Milford Central School; Time: Saturday, April 9 (11:00 am - 3:00 pm). Enjoy exhibits, activities and entertainment. Bring along your recyclables to be collected. You'll go green! Fashion Show will be held at the end of the day. Admis...\n\nQ: This passage was written mainly for   _  .s6t----", "options": ["students who study at Milford Central School, New Yorks6t----", "people who want to attend Earth Day events in the Catskill regions6t----", "adults who protect the environment in New Yorks6t----", "people who celebrate Earth Day all over the worlds6t----"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1481, "question": "A person named Bernard Jackson today is a free man, but he has many bitter memories. He spent five years in prison after a jury wrongly convicted (...) him of raping two women. At Jackson's trial, although two witnesses testified that Jackson was with them in another location at the time of the crime, he was convicted anyway. Why? The jury believed the testimony of the two victims, who positively identified Jackson as the man who had attacked them. The court eventually freed Jackson after the police found the real criminal. Many factors influence the accuracy of eyewitness testimony. For instance, witnesses sometimes see photographs of several suspects before they try to identify the person they saw in a group of people. They can become confused by seeing many photographs of similar faces....\n\nQ: According to the text, we can infer that    _   .", "options": ["eyewitness testimony is valuable, though sometimes incorrect.", "police identification is more reliable than that of the ordinary people", "crime victims often fail to give positive identification of the suspects", "the jury relies on the judge than the eyewitness for a decision"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 535, "question": "Two studies are suggesting that some overweight people do not face an increased risk of developing heart disease. Researchers also found that some individuals of normal body weight have an increased risk of the disease. Being overweight does increase your risk of medical problems, but the studies found that not all heavy people are less healthy than thin people. In one study, American researchers examined medical records from over 5000 men and women. Each person had taken part in a separate study from 1999 to 2004. The searchers found that about 51% of them were overweight or obese. About 32% were obese, but considered metabolically healthy. This means they had no evidence of problems in tests for high blood pressure or other factors linked to heart disease. However, more than 23% of peopl...\n\nQ: Professor WylieRosett agrees that people should  _  .", "options": ["avoid becoming obese", "not worry about becoming obese", "worry about becoming thin", "not be afraid of several diseases"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 310, "question": "When we say older people shrink, we don't mean they become tiny enough to fit in your pocket! We just mean that it's common for older people to become a little shorter over time. This kind of shrinking can't be reversed, although people can slow or stop this process. But why does shrinking happen at all? Because of gravity (the force that keeps your feet on the ground) , cushions between the bones in the spine , get compressed , which makes a person lose a little height and become shorter. Another reason why some older people shrink is because of osteoporosis . Osteoporosis occurs when bone is broken down and not enough new bone material is made. Over time, bone is said to be lost because it's not being replaced. Bones become smaller and weaker and can easily break if someone with osteopor...\n\nQ: About osteoporosis, we know that   _  .", "options": ["gravity is one of the causes of osteoporosis", "once our bone is broken down, osteoporosis will occur", "women are more likely to develop osteoporosis", "if we develop osteoporosis, we are more likely to be shorter"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 594, "question": "In most of the time, I am devoted to my research in the lab with my friend Dave, who loves traveling very much. To make our life colorful and relax ourselves, in July, my friend and I are taking a camping trip. We will travel for four weeks and will tour the United States and part of Canada. We have decided to camp because it does not cost as much as vacationing in hotels. We have to plan very carefully in advance. First, the car we are going to drive is very small, so we have decided to take only one small suitcase each and as few camping things as possible. We will take some medicine with us to prevent insects from hurting us, and also food for picnics. Second, there is a lot to see in the United States and Canada, so we have to decide on the direction we want to drive. The date we are l...\n\nQ: It is quite clear that   _  .", "options": ["there will be no insects at all.", "they are sure to take some medicine on the trip.", "the two friends will take turns to drive.", "the two friends will share a suitcase."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 162, "question": "There is no doubt about it.The best way to learn new words is to do it unconsciously.I don't mean while you're unconscious.I mean while you are unconscious of the fact that it is sinking in. That is how I learnt the 30,000 words in my vocabulary by living in an English-speaking world, mother tongue.I just pick them up.But some of _ may be misunderstood.Now, to misunderstand does not mean not to understand.To misunderstand is to understand but incorrectly. The 5 % mislearnt of all the words we \"know\" will be the least frequently used words, as the more frequently used words are less likely to be mislearnt.Some of the misunderstandings may live with all our lives, without knowing that we got them wrong. Many English teachers think that this natural method of learning words in one's own mothe...\n\nQ: Which of the following is most likely NOT true?", "options": ["Some of the words the writer knows must have been misunderstood.", "Most of the 30,000 words the writer learned are frequently used ones.", "How many words the writer got wrong are not known.", "All the words the writer knows were learned by reading them."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 728, "question": "Expensive and new gloves allow chatterboxes to take the term \"handsfree\" to a new level--by talking into them as they make a call. The gloves are known as \"Talk to the Hand\" and cost PS1,000 a pair. They fixed a speaker unit into the thumb and a microphone into the little finger that can be connected to any mobile handset using Bluetooth. Artist Sean Miles designed the new gloves that double as a phone in part of his project that shows the possibilities of gadget(,) recycling. He uses outdated gloves and combines them with parts from mobile handsets recycled through _ , which commissioned the project. Mobile phone users will be able to keep their hands warm while they chat without taking their phones out of their pockets or handbags. Mr Miles designed two pairs of the new gloves--one in pi...\n\nQ: What is the passage mainly about?", "options": ["New mobiles that are fashionable.", "Outdated handsets that are upgraded.", "Outdated gadgets that can be used for recycling.", "New gloves that can be used for making phone calls."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1641, "question": "Have you ever tried broccoli ice cream? That's what Oliver serves his customers in the new movie Oliver's Organic Ice Cream. The one-minute film was created by kids. A film is a movie. The young students learned their moviemaking skills at the Jacob Burns Film Center. The center is in Pleasantville, New York. Kids who go there learn how to make movies and music videos. The character Oliver and his treats are animated. In an animated movie, objects, such as ice cream and paper dolls, appear to be alive or moving. Animated movies are made up of hundreds of pictures. It takes 15 pictures to make just one second of film. To make a movie that lasts one minute, students need to take about 900 frames. A frame is a picture. Animation expert Joe Summerhays teaches kids the steps to shoot a movie. H...\n\nQ: If Jim wants to make a 5 minutes animated movie, he needs to take about   _  .", "options": ["10 pictures", "15 pictures", "900 pictures", "4500 pictures"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 716, "question": "Microblogging is a broadcast medium in the form of blogging. A microblog differs from a traditional blog in that its content is typically much smaller, in both actual size and aggregate file size. Microblogs \"allow users to exchange small elements of content such as short sentences, individual images, or video links\". As with traditional blogging, microbloggers post about topics ranging from the simple, such as \"what I'm doing right now,\" to the thematic , such as \"sports cars.\" Commercial microblogs also exist, to promote websites, services and/or products, and to promote collaboration within an organization. Some microblogging services offer features such as privacy settings, which allow users to control who can read their microblogs, or other ways of publishing rights besides entering t...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that  _  .", "options": ["microbloggers always post about the thematic topics instead of the simple ones", "microblogging has developed so quickly and brought the owners more and more benefits.", "microblogging protects both the owners' and the readers' privacy", "the studies by Harvard Business School have analyzed the usage of microblogging services"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 378, "question": "Two thieves came to a house to steal something. They dug a hole in the wall of the house. There lived many mice in the house. The woman in the house saw a mouse crawl into the house in the moonlight. \"Look! In comes one,\" she said to the man in the house. The thief was so frightened that he hurriedly crawled out of the house and said to the one waiting outside, \"She found me when I was just in.\" But the thief outside didn't believe him, so he said, \"Let us try to crawl into the house together.\" At that time two mice happened to crawl into the house, too. The woman saw the mice and shouted, \"In come two, catch them!\" The two thieves were terribly frightened. The man in the house said, \"You saw them come in but where are they? I will catch them tonight.\" The two thieves started running away ...\n\nQ: When the woman said, \"How they look like the two of last night!\"   _  .", "options": ["she referred to the two thieves", "she meant nothing", "she said it on purpose", "she referred to the mice"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1513, "question": "Going green seems to be a fad for a lot of people these days.Whether that is good or bad,we can't really say, but for the two of us, going green is not a fad but a life style. On April 22,2011,we decided to be green every single day for an entire year. This meant doing 365 different things, and it also meant challenging ourselves to go green beyond the easy things. Rather than recycle and reduce our energy, we had to think of 365 diffenent things to do and this was no easy task. With the idea of going green every single day a year,Our Greean Year started. My wife and I decided to educate people about how they could go green in their lives and hoped we could show people all green things that could be done to help the environment. We wanted to push the message that every little bit helps. Ov...\n\nQ: What did the couple do over the course of Our Green Year?", "options": ["They tried to get out of their ungreen habits.", "They ignored others' ungreen behaviour.", "They chose better chemical cleaners.", "they sold their home-made food"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2402, "question": "European Work Experience Program(E.W.E.P.)is an independent British organization which began in 1991 in the city of London.E.W.E.P.provides the opportunity for students from the 25 countries of the European Union and nationals from Norway,Iceland,Switzerland and Liechtenstein to live in England,to gain work experience,to practice their English and to get a better insight into the British social and eulturallife. To apply you must meet the following requirements: *Preferred age: 18 to 28 years old *Be able to work in the UK for a period of at least two months. *Must have a good knowledge of English. *Due to work permit restrictions,European Work Experience Program Ltd will only select you if you are a European Union Member or national from Norway,Iceland,Switzerland and Liechtenstein. Europ...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE according to the text?", "options": ["European Work Experience Program Was set up in the 19th century.", "You'll work in the UK for at least two months if you attend the program.", "You can get a 24-hour help from a representative during your stay.", "You don't have to hand in 394.35 Euros after you have got a job in Britain."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2248, "question": "Experts say that students usually need eight to ten hours' sleep at night, but most Chinese students do not get enough sleep. Some Chinese parents are usually glad to see their children study late. They will think their children work very hard. But not all parents are happy about this. Once a mother told us that every morning her 10-year-old boy put up one finger with his eyes still closed, begging for one more minute to sleep. Like thousands of students \"early birds\" in China, he has to get up before six every morning. A report shows that without a good night's sleep, students seem to be weaker than they should be. Many students have fallen asleep during class at one time or another. Too much homework is not the only reason why students stay up late. Some watch TV or play the computer gam...\n\nQ: Experts have told us students should   _  .", "options": ["get enough sleep", "not get enough sleep", "study late", "sleep less"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1024, "question": "Did the iPod kill music ? DID Steve Jobs kill the music industry? That's the question on many people's lips since rock star Jon Bon Jovi accused the apple boss of personally destroying the music industry. Bon Jovi centers his criticism on how he believes music downloading has robbed young people of what he calls the \"beauty of buying on album\", \"Kids today have missed the beauty of taking your allowance money and making a decision based on the _ , not knowing what the record sounded like,\" he said. But far from killing the industry, many young people today think Jobs has been a blessing , offering you instant, and selective access to a whole world of music. Keith Staskiewicz at Entertainment Weekly speaks for the feelings of many music lovers. He believes listening to Mp3s rather than reco...\n\nQ: According to Mark Mulligan, the best solution to illegal music downloading is to   _  .", "options": ["legalize music downloading via sites like iTunes", "ban the illegal music downloading sites on the Internet", "help young consumers get used to paying for music", "offer young consumers instant and selective access to a variety of music"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3477, "question": "Once upon a time, on an isolated island in the Java sea, lived short people who dominated(, ) the food chain. Standing no more than three and a half feet tall, these human ancestors hunted giant rats, lumbering lizards , and _ elephants. It sounds a bit like a fairy tale, but it's true. Unearthed relics on the island uncovered the remains of a race of tiny human ancestors. Homo floresiensis, as the newly discovered species has been named, apparently could date back to 13,000 years ago. This means they have a lot in common with modern humans. So how and why did these people get so small? Scientists suspect that it's due to the fact that this race lived on an isolated island with limited resources. Take the miniature elephants for example. When elephants first came to the island either by sw...\n\nQ: People on the island got so small because  _  .", "options": ["they did not have enough food to eat.", "they gradually developed for lack of food.", "they shared less food with elephants.", "they remained alive as the elephants."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1412, "question": "Some children are natural-born bosses. They have a strong need to make decisions, manage their environment, and lead rather than follow. Stephen Jackson, a Year One student, \"operates under the theory of what's mine is mine and what's yours is mine,\" says his mother. \"The other day I bought two new Star Wars light sabers . Later, I saw Stephen with the two new ones while his brother was using the beat-up ones. \" \"Examine the extended family, and you'll probably find a bossy grandparent, aunt, uncle or cousin in every generation. It's an inheritable trait,\" says Russell Barkley, a professor at the Medical University of South Carolina. Other children who may not be particularly bossy can gradually gain dominance when they sense their parents are weak, hesitant, or in disagreement with each o...\n\nQ: Bossy children like Stephen Jackson  _  .", "options": ["make good decisions", "show self-centeredness", "lack care from others", "have little sense of fear"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 800, "question": "We all use money every day. It is essential because we can pay money for whatever we want.Money is recognized as banknotes and coins. However,many years ago people couldn' t go to the shop and buy what they wanted.They had to get what they wanted through the barter trade .It was really difficult,for the barter often depended on coincidence of wants.For example,the seller of grain has to find a buyer who wants to buy grain and who also could offer something the seller wants to buy.And one more example,if a wheat farmer needs what a fruit farmer produces,a direct exchange is impossible because seasonal fruit would spoil before the grain harvest.The solution is to trade fruit for wheat indirectly through a third intermediate commodity ,such as cattle,salt,shells,wine.However,commodity money h...\n\nQ: Paper money was used earlier in  _  .", "options": ["Rome", "Greece", "the USA", "the Netherlands"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 804, "question": "Studies show that you may be lied to every day anywhere from 10 to 200 times. We say, \"Nice song.\" \"Honey, you don't look fat in that, no.\" But another study showed that strangers lied three times within the first 10 minutes of meeting each other. We lie more to strangers than we lie to coworkers. Men lie eight times more about themselves than they do other people. Women lie more to protect other people. If you're married, you're going to lie to your wife/ husband in one out of every 10 communications. If you're unmarried, that number drops to three. But look, if at some point you got lied to, it's because you agreed to get lied to. Truth about lying: lying's a cooperative act. Not all lies are harmful. Sometimes we're willing to lie for the sake of social dignity , maybe to keep a private...\n\nQ: Lying is complex because   _  .", "options": ["it is practiced by clever ones", "people are for it as well as against it", "ancient stories are full of lies", "it is the whole part of great culture"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 31, "question": "What does it mean to say that we live in a world of persuasion? It means that we live among competing interests. Your roommate's need to study for an exam may take priority over pizza. Your instructor may have good reasons not to change your grade. In such a world, persuasion is the art of getting others to give fair and favorable consideration to our points of view. When we persuade, we want to influence how others believe and behave. We may not always _ -- other points of view may be more persuasive, depending on the listener, the situation, and the merit of the case. But when we practice the art of persuasion, we try to ensure that our position receives the attention it deserves. Some people, however, object to the very idea of persuasion. They may regard it as an unwelcome interruption...\n\nQ: According to the passage, persuasion means   _  .", "options": ["changing others' points of view", "exercising power over other people", "getting other people to consider your point of view", "getting people to agree with you and do what you want"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3436, "question": "A quarter of US adults say they read no books at all in the past year, according to an Associated Press-Ipsos survey. The typical person said that he / she read four books in the last year and, excluding those who had not read any books at all, the usual number of books read was seven. Of those who did read, women and pensioners were the most eager readers, and religious works and popular fiction were the top choices. The number of books read was nine books for women and five for men. The number also showed that those with college degrees read the most, and people aged 50 and over read more than those who are younger. People from the West and Midwest are more likely to have read at least one book in the past year. Southerners who do read tend to read more books -- mostly religious books an...\n\nQ: What kind of books was read most according to the passage?", "options": ["Religious works.", "Popular fiction.", "Poetry.", "History."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 534, "question": "Two studies are suggesting that some overweight people do not face an increased risk of developing heart disease. Researchers also found that some individuals of normal body weight have an increased risk of the disease. Being overweight does increase your risk of medical problems, but the studies found that not all heavy people are less healthy than thin people. In one study, American researchers examined medical records from over 5000 men and women. Each person had taken part in a separate study from 1999 to 2004. The searchers found that about 51% of them were overweight or obese. About 32% were obese, but considered metabolically healthy. This means they had no evidence of problems in tests for high blood pressure or other factors linked to heart disease. However, more than 23% of peopl...\n\nQ: What was found in 23% of the healthy people examined?", "options": ["No factors linked to heart disease.", "They were unhealthy in two or more aspects.", "High blood pressure.", "No evidence of problems."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2789, "question": "While the other kids seemed excited about celebrating the end-of-term party by playing games and sharing treats, Jeremy hated the very idea of the gathering. Afraid to raise the pressure too high, I decided to contribute something that was easy to purchase on the walk to school. Off we went the day of the party, approaching his school as if nothing was planned. I reminded him of our need to make a purchase, entered his favorite shop, and asked him to select the ripest bunch of grapes. He shot me an anxious look and insisted none of his classmates ever be able to notice he had something to bring to the party. My _ of a successful parenting method, resulting in delivering a sociable child to his school, diverted sharply from reality. Back on route, I did my best to hide the sinking feeling o...\n\nQ: Why did the author hurry to her son's classroom?", "options": ["She went to ask the teacher for help.", "She went there to give her lesson.", "She was afraid of her son being punished.", "She was invited to take part in the celebration."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3446, "question": "Study Books Basic Study Manual Hardcover :$ 37 Future success depends on the ability to learn. Here are the answers to the questions most often asked by parents, teachers, business trainers and by students themselves. Read this book and learn: What the three barriers to study are and what to do about them. What to do if you get tired of a subject you are studying. Twenty-six simple drills to help you learn how to study easily, rapidly and with full understanding. Buy and read Basic Study Manual and use it do dramatically improve your ability to study. Study Skills for Life Hardcover: $32 L. Ron Hubbard's study technology for children opens the door to their future success by giving them the ability to study and learn. Fully illustrated (,) for easy comprehension. Learning How to Learn Hard...\n\nQ: Some of the four books were illustrated in order to   _  .", "options": ["persuade foreigners to buy all of them", "reduce the cost of them", "help readers understand them and make a better choice", "make them suitable to different reader."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2299, "question": "Law School Essays that Made a Difference Price: US $ 13.95 Paperback 256 pages The Princeton Review ISBN: 0375763457 Face it, and a lot of students have great LSAT scores. The best way for you to stand out in a crowd of applicants to top law schools is to write an exceptional(,) personal statement. This book puts you in the admissions office's seat. It gives you the intimate detailstest scores, GPAs (grade point average), demographic information, and personal statementsof 34 law school hopefuls, then shows you why they got into the colleges they applied to, and why some didn't. It's invaluable information that will help students evaluate their own chances of admission to the most selective law schools in the United States. Business School Essays that Made a Difference Price: US $ 13.95 Pap...\n\nQ: LSAT is most probably   _  .", "options": ["an admission test given by a law school", "a test for admitted law students", "information on business and college", "information on GPA"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3397, "question": "Women love shoes! They will sometimes go to look for the perfect pair of shoes to wear only once with the perfect outfit or the fashion of the day. Once worn, these fashionable designer shoes may spend weeks, months, or years in the closet without being worn again until another special occasion comes up. With that said, are expensive designer shoes really worth their cost? Historically, shoes were invented to free feet from sharp rocks, hot sands, and blisters. Shoes were made to be simple and functional, with tough leather soles and straps. As society became more sophisticated , the role of shoes changed; shoes were made to add status to the wearer. Shoe designers began to work on the production of fashion shoes for the wealthy; shoes meant more for show than for practical use or simplici...\n\nQ: From the passage, we can learn that   _  .", "options": ["women like to wear designer shoes only during the workday", "designer shoes are more practical and beautiful than common shoes", "shoemakers won fame for their shoes' prices", "shoemakers printed symbols on their shoes for being recognized"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2107, "question": "Ann was on her first package trip in Rosas, Spain. At the hotel, she checked in, and then went to her room to change before dinner. She was just ready to go downstairs when she found that her Spanish money wasn't in her handbag. She carefully looked in all her luggage, but she couldn't find it. All she had was a small purse with ten English pound notes in it! Ann found a place to change her English money. She had very few pesetas , and she would be here for two weeks. On her way back to the hotel, Ann bought some cheese, some bread and some oranges. When she got back, she told the manager that her doctor had told her not to eat Spanish food; she'd just have breakfast each day. That was all right, as she knew the price of hotels included breakfast. For the rest of her holiday, Ann swam in t...\n\nQ: Ann didn't eat dinners in the restaurant of the hotel because   _  .", "options": ["she wasn't well", "her doctor told her not to eat them", "she was afraid that she couldn't pay for them with her little money", "she wasn't hungry"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2461, "question": "With a good shopping position and the right amount of money , any educated person ought to be able to make a living out of a bookshop . It is not a difficult trade to learn and the large chain-stores can never force the small bookseller out of existence as they have done to the corner shop . But the hours of work are very long-I was only doing a part-time job , but my boss put in a seventy-hour week ,besides regular journeys out of shopping hours to buy books . The real reason why I should not like to be back in the book trade for life , however , is that while I was in it, I lost my love of books . A bookseller cannot always tell the truth about his books , and that gives him a dislike for them . There was a time when I really did love books--loved the sight and smell and feel of them--if...\n\nQ: The books preferred by the author should be those_.", "options": ["stories making readers sleepless", "valuable ones bought on sale", "peculiar ones with great expectation", "geography ones from the eighteenth century"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 234, "question": "For 52 years my father got up at 5:30 am every morning, went to work, and returned home at 5:30 pm. I never saw my father stayed home from work ill, nor did I ever see my father lay down to take a nap. He had no hobbies, other than taking care of his family. All he asked from me, his daughter, was to help him while he was repairing something, so we could have some time to talk. For 22 years, after I left home for college, my father called me at 9:00 am every Sunday. Nine years ago when I bought my first house, my father, 67 years old, spent eight hours a day for three days painting my house. He would not allow me to pay someone to have it done. All he asked for was a glass of iced tea. Five years ago, at age 71, my father spent five hours putting together a swing set for my daughter. On th...\n\nQ: The author wrote the article in order to   _  .", "options": ["praise her father", "remember her father", "show her father loved her", "let her father be known"], "answer": 1}]